Guide to the Kenneth M. Cuthbertson Papers SC0582
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-021
  - Endowments (Thursday 5/12 10am) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Endowments, Incorporated 1976 (Box 58, Folder 4-10)
  - Endowments, Incorporated (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Endowments, Incorporated - Newhouse Foundation (Box 59, Folder 2-5)
  - Newhouse Foundation 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
  - Newhouse Foundation 1973 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Newhouse Foundation 1972 (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
  - Newhouse Foundation 1972 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Capital Research and Management, Incorporated (Box 60, Folder 3-7)
  - Capital Research and Management Corporation (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Capital Research and Management Corporation (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Newhouse Foundation, Incorporated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Endowments (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Land and Buildings (Box 61, Folder 4-7)
  - Investments (Box 61, Folder 8-10)
  - Ad Hoc Capital Facilities Committee (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Trustee Dinners (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Trustees - 1975 (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
  - Trustees - 1974 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Trustees - 1973 (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
  - Trustees - 1972 (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
  - Trustees - 1971 and earlier (Box 62, Folder 11-13)
  - Trustees - 1971 and earlier (4 of 6) (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
  - Delegation of Authority (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Delegation of Powers (Box 63, Folder 5-7)
  - Proxies (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Signature Resolutions (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Staff/Student Involvement (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Student Development (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Programs (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - SWOPSI (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Tuition (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - ACE - American Council on Education (Box 64, Folder 4-7)
  - AAFRC - American Association of Fund-Raising Counsel, Incorporated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - ARPA Meeting (Advanced Research Project Agency) (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - BLC Members (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - California Postsecondary Education Commission (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - CAUSE - College and University Systems Exchange (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - CED - Committee for Economic Development (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - AICCU (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - AICUM - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities of Michigan (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - AGB Reports (Association of Governing Boards) (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Sponsored Projects (Box 65, Folder 3-5)
  - Stanford Facts (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Magazine (Box 65, Folder 7-8)
  - Stanford in: Washington and Sacramento (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Name (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Observatory (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Shopping Center (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Taxes - Tax Laws (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Tax Incentive Equalization Proposal (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Taxes - Non-Residents (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Taxes - Property Tax Problems (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Teaching Assistants (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Tour Guides (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Uncommon Man (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - University Advisory Committee (New) (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Scholars (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Word Processing Center (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Youth Opportunity Program (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - A.R.L.O. (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
  - A.S.S.U. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Banking (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Report on "The Costs of Higher Education in California," 1960 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Black Student Union (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Foreign students (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Indians / Native Americans (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Commencement (Box 66, Folder 14-15)
  - Employment (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
  - Housing - Fraternities (Box 67, Folder 5-9)
  - Housing - Married Students (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Students (Box 67, Folder 11-12)
  - Housing - Students (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - Campaign - General (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Campaign project group (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Campaign planning budgets (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Goals and Planning [1971-72] (Box 68, Folder 7-12)
  - Organization (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Planning - staffing (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Student participation - leadership (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Matching gift - faculty/staff program (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Women in the Campaign (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Draft of campaign plan (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Case statement (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Case statement - KMC notes (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Case statement 1972 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Case statement #2, 4/71 - 12/71 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Case statement #3, 1/72 - 3/72 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Council for Opportunity in Graduate Management Education (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - College and University Reporter Advisory Editorial Board (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Endowment Conference - N.Y. April 1969 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Harvard Club (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Industry-Education Council of California (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Association of American Universities (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Amer. Assoc. of University Professors (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - ACPRA Conference (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Title VI. Of Civil Rights Act of 1964 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - American Alumni Council Conference (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - State Aid (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Taxes - California State Sale and Income Tax (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Court Appearance (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Western Assoc. of Schools and Colleges (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - WACUBO (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Post Campaign Planning (Box 70, Folder 10-13)
  - Annual Fund Long Range Planning (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund Challenge Gift (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Re-Commitment Effort (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Budget Post Campaign (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - GSO Retreats/Meeting (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Status Progress (Box 71, Folder 8-10)
  - Charts/Campaign (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
  - Robert Conway Memos (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Consultant, Study of (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Conway, Robert L. - John Price Jones Company (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Inner Quad KMC Volunteer Activities (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - KMC Volunteer Activities (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - The Campaign for Stanford--Campaign Plans (Confidential) (Box 72, Folder 5-7)
  - Stanford in the Seventies--Preliminary Case Statement Outline 7/1/70 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - An Interim Report to The President of Stanford University on the University's Fund Raising Structure, Policies and Procedures (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Announcement (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Anniversary Announcement (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Newsletter (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, News Releases (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - PACE History File (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Publications Program (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Comparisons: PACE/Campaign for Stanford (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Publicity (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - $200 Million Announcement (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - 1974-1976 Campaign Anniversary (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Case Statement #1 12/69-3/71 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Communications and publications (Box 73, Folder 11-14)
  - Annual Fund (Box 73, Folder 15-17)
  - Annual Fund (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - IRS Audit (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - University Seminar Nov. 1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Federal Tax Legislation (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Phase IV (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Foundations (Box 74, Folder 6-11)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Fulbright (Mansfield) Amendment. 1970 Military Authorization and Appropriations Bills (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Government Policies - student disruption riders (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Governmental Relations (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers 1971 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Association of Bay Area Governments (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on California Solicitation (Box 75, Folder 2-5)
  - California Tomorrow Plan (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - State Constitution - Revision (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - State - Legislative matters misc. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - California Legislature (Joint Committee on Higher Education) (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Filer Commission on Private Philanthropy and Public Needs (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Taxable Income Survey (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Tax Laws (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Taxes - Tax Reform (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Uniform Management of Institutional Funds Act (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Government Congressional Record (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Urban Coalition (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee Pacific School of Religion (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Speeches--Speech Material (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Earth Day--Panel Comments KMC 4/22/70 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - KMC Campaign Talks and Speeches (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Conference Speech September 24, 25 1971 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Special Gifts (Box 76, Folder 7-9)
  - Southern California/Phoenix (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - Parents (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Conferences (Box 77, Folder 4-7)
  - Leadership Meetings (Box 77, Folder 8-10)
  - Inner Quad (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
  - Inner Quad (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund Division Reports (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - General Projects Including International Fund Raising (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Northern California and Hawaii (Box 78, Folder 4-6)
  - East Pennsylvania (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - East Washington D.C. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Fellowships (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Lectureships (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Professorships Endowed/Other (Box 78, Folder 11-12)
  - Professorships Endowed/Other (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 79, Folder 3-5)
  - Status of Campaign (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Asks (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - GSO-Ex-Comm. Meetings (Box 79, Folder 8-9)
  - Prospects (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Status Reports (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Status Reports (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Major Gifts Plan (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Major Gifts Forecast (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - East New York (Box 80, Folder 5-8)
  - East New England (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer Meetings (Box 80, Folder 10-13)
  - Volunteers--Faculty (Box 80, Folder 1416)
  - Seminars (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Seminars (Box 81, Folder 1-6)
  - Corporations (Box 81, Folder 7-11)
  - Midwest (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Budget (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Summer School Staff Training O.O.D Budget (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Budget Presentation, 5-21-91 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Gift Comparisons for Liaison Team (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Budget 5/90 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Office of Development (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Budget (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Office of Development 3-year Budget Plan 1991/92 - 1993/94 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Budget Liaison Team Transparencies (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Objectives Near West 1985 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Objectives Near West (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Near West Campus (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
  - Near West Campus Writing Project (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Near West/Science Centers (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Near West Campus Plan. Summary Planning Report. January 1987 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Near West [Campus] Solicitation (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Near West Campus 1989-90 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Campaign Objectives Near West 1988 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Public Service Center Annual Report 1987-88 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - TAC meetings Near West Campus 1986 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Near West Campus Jan. - Apr. 1988 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - NWC Task Force - Fundraising Strategy (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Near West Campus Committee (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Campaign Objectives Near West 1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Campaign Objectives Near West 1986 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Bacchetti Papers (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Conceptual Definition (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Key Papers; DFK, Gibbons, etc. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Near West Campus Alternatives January 1987 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Sequencing and critical path 1988-89 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, Stanford University (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Photon Science (P.E.R.L.) (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Strategy and Estimates (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Book I and Book II from TAC (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - NWC Planning Staff (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Biology (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - NWC Name (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Futures: papers, responses (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Specific Donor Proposals (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Draft. Stanford University Information Sciences Building Program. Prepared by ROMA Design Group, October 1989 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Information Sciences (Computer Science, etc.) (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - C. I. S. expansion (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Connective Elements (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Near West Campus. Connective Elements Projects. Stanf. Univ., Sept. '89. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - NWC Management Group (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - NWC Updates (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Advanced Materials Research (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Governmental Relations - Subcommittee on Education (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Federal Budgets (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Federal Government: Financing Higher Education (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Federal Government: "Freeze" on federal funds 4/67 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Federal Institution Aid (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Governmental Policies (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Injunction - hearing, Mar. 1-2, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Development in Higher Education (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Listening Post (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Mission Coalition Organization (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - National Association of College and University Attorneys (NACUA) (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (Bonnen - Michigan State U.) (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - National Council on Philanthropy (DSJ) (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - NCATE (National Commission on the Accreditation of Teacher Education) (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Preferred Fund (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Preferred Fund Access to Prospects (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Dual Solicitation 1970 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Final Report. President's Centennial Discussion. August 1986 (2 copies) (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - President's Centennial Discussions Final Report for Staff Use October 1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Computer printouts (Box 87, Folder 5-8)
  - Computer printouts (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Travel Task Force (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
  - Travel Task Force 1/29/92 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Post Campaign Organization (Old Background and General) (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Law Schools Section on Institutional Advancement--Law School Development Survey 1988-89 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - President's Centennial Discussion Final Report for Staff Use, October 1986 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - PCD Follow-up Letters, Sue Nelson (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - History Centennial Campaign, 1986-1992 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Draft 5/20/93--The History of the Stanford Centennial Campaign (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 30 Presidential Discussion (Letter File) (Box 89, Folder 4-5)
  - Special Analyses (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Committee on Culture, Final Report (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Planning (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Final Report of the Office of Development Long Range Planning Committee, Stanford University, November 1989 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
  - Repositioning Task Force (Box 90, Folder 4-7)
  - Centennial Task Force Planning Committee (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Task Force Planning Committee (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
  - Centennial Campaign: Revised Panning Timeline (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Planning-Thru 1982 I (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Planning-Thru 1982 II (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Task Forces--Kennedy Task Force on Objectives (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Planning Task Force (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Campaign Case Statement (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Planning 1983 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Matching Funds (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Various Months and Conference Calls (Box 92, Folder 3-5)
  - Co-Chair Meeting November 18, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee Meeting October 12, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Co-Chair Meeting October 12, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Co-Chair Meeting August 29, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Co-Chair Meeting July 11, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Steering Committee Meeting May 23, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Co-Chair Meeting May11, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Co-Chair Meeting March 15, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Steering Committee Meeting February 9, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Co-Chair Meeting February 9, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Co-Chair Meeting January 7, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting November 20, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting October 22, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting September 28, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee Meeting May 15, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting May 13, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting April 17, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Consultants (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council 1984/1985 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Dinners (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Centennial Dinner Guests (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Washington, D.C. Centennial Discussion Dinner, April 21, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Comments--Centennial Luncheons and Dinners (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary June 1941 Activities (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary 10/11/41 Dinner (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Oct 1 to 5 activities except 10/1 dinner (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary General Planning (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Chamber of Commerce Luncheon 5/14/41 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Studies made of celebrations by other univ. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Gifts and Pledges Policy and Procedure for Handling 1961 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Gifts and Pledges Policy and Procedure for Handling 1962-1964 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - $1,000 Daily Report January 6, 1967-August 31, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - $1,000 Daily Report September 9, 1966-December 30, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Daily $1,000 Gift Reports 7/1/66-8/31/66 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Daily Gift Report 7/1/65-6/30/66 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Daily Gift Report 9/1/64-6/30/65 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Gift Reports--Monthly September 1960-61 thru September 1962-63 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Development Gift Reports--Monthly August 1960 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Gifts 1960: Report of Gifts and Grants Received (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Gift Reports--1945-46 thru 1953-54 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Gifts: Reports of Significant Gifts 1960-1964 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Gifts with Reservations on Life Income--Stanford Policy 1/55-12/57 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Gifts with Reservation on Life Income--Stanford Policy thru 12/54 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Gift Reports--Monthly September 1962-63 thru August 1964-65 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Gifts From Foundation, Corporations and Associations 9/24-6/43 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Special gift Committee 1948-9/1/54 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Gift Program Development 1940-1945 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - How Rich is Stanford (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Special Gifts Committee (1948-49) Coordinating Committee for Gift Procurement (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Gifts Statistics (Various Reports Prepared by Stanford 1959) (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Statistics 1940-49 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Gift Procurement and Public Relations (Development under Ray Lyman Wilbur 1928-44) (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Gifts Statistics--Various Reports Prepared Comparison--other schools 1968 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Admissions 1967-68 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Admissions 1966-67 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Admissions 1965-66 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Admissions 1964-65 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Admissions 1963-64 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Admissions 1962-63 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Admissions 1961-62 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Admissions 1959-60, 1960-61 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Admissions 1958-59 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Admissions 1957-58 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Admissions 1956-57 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Admissions 1955-56 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Admissions 1954-55 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Admissions 1953-54 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Admissions 1952-1953 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Admissions 1951-1952 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Admissions High School Relations (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Registrations and Academic Standing, Committee on (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Registrar Summer Workshops and Seminars 1969 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Department 1959 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1963 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1962 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1961 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1960 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1958-1959 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1957-1958 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1956-1957 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1955-1956 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1954-1955 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1953-1954 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1952-1953 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Courtesy List 1942-1951 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Pavilion 1966 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Buck Club 1964-1969 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Buck Club 1958-1963 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Buck Club 1957 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Buck Club Minutes of Meeting (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Football 1966 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Football 1965 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Football 1964 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Football Tickets 1963 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Football 1963-64 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Football 1962 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Football Fall 1961 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Football Fall 1960 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Football 1959 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Football Fall 1958 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Football Big Game 1957 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Football Big Game 1956 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Football Big Game 1955 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Football 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Football 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Football 1949, 1950, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Football 1947, 1948, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Football Ticket Preference System (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Football Ticket Preference System, Complaints (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Football - Rose Bowl (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Minorities Budgeting (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Minorities, Employment of (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Minorities Commitments (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Monterey Institute of Foreign Studies (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Music Department (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - "N" Old (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - NEA National Education Association (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - NIH (National Institute of Health) Training Grants, ect. (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - New Hospital Planning (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - "O" Old (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - O'Brien, Richard F. (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Oil and Gas Properties (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Operations Research Space (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Organized Research and Financing (research contracts and grants) (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - "P" Old (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto Stanford Hospital Center (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Parking Regulations (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Personnel 1967 (Fringe Benefits etc.) (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Personnel 1964-1966 incl. (Fringe Benefits etc.) (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Committees (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Professorships (Old) (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Projects Review and Sign Off (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Proprietary Rights in Data (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Public v. Private (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - "R" old (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Radiotherapy Center (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Regional Medical Program (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Religious Studies (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Religious Activities Report (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Research at Stanford 1968-69 (Box 103, Folder 13)